ninety-two we bought a v8 Robo from the
wreckers petrol at that stage was 42
cents a litre government always tells
the truth
they said the petrol I'll never ever
exceed 42 cents a liter
one week later after we had the car on
the road it hit 53 and rising quickly
I just went grab this stainless steel
from the scrap yards through it all
together into some weed order I don't
even know why how are you on a Friday
afternoon which was my son's birthday
the 9th of October I threw it onto a car
this was on the rover this so now I
didn't hook it up to the carburetor to
the intake I don't even know why I put
it where I put it but it ended up going
hooking a plane straight water through
these neutral place onto heat exchange
on the 79 rover sd1 3500 not
fuel-injected juice carburetor
disconnected all the fuel lines all the
feel everything else
disconnect them not left them on pull
them all off hit the key dampening run
dojo so is claimed to function something
like this it starts with the water tap
water goes into a conditioning tumbler a
series of magnetic plates with
electrical negatively charged the water
local period of hours this negatively
charged water goes into the South
katooni electric current is applied for
a short period inside the cell
stainless tube was which are positioned
in preparations of the golden mean
ratios receive an oscillating DC current
by tweaking this combination of
frequencies created that allows water to
break into its two parts easily hydrogen
is fed directly into the carburetor
replacing the technology if it works the
Jo cell is a standalone onboard energy
device
it's claimed to get about a hundred
kilometers per card
the whole idea behind hydrogen fuels is
basically a version of that but the fact
is that it takes a lot of energy to
separate oxygen and hydrogen in order to
break up warm water molecules you need
to put in a lot of energy to break the
bonds so that when you burn hydrogen
again it's urgent liberate a lot of
energy and becomes water again you got
the fat guy there we put the cell
together and put on his rover and lo and
behold it continued to running after we
turn the fuel off so we looked at each
other and said Ryder where's the can of
camera I think just couldn't be this
simple I'd never seen I've never done
the day science that I know anything
about hydrogen oxygen gas as such don't
know about your brown anybody like it
never knew anything about anything as
such and I do know a hell of all about
mechanics pretty good breeze on that
this balloon is gonna do one of three
things one is it's going to implode and
find and turn the balloon inside other
than in rushing air is going to take
every hair off me or everything else the
second thing that's if we've got the in
place is gas straight off we've got
these bubbles will trickle over here
near here on this
[Music]
[Applause]
the yellow flank to the blend fragmented
and we've got a frequency unit which is
hydrogen that's a low negative way this
is power off
[Music]
over unity devices are sometimes called
free energy devices and we say that is a
an inappropriate use of language because
clearly the electric inertia that comes
from the gravity field due to fractality
is not free and there's a price to be
paid in the case of specifically
hydrogen implosion devices the inertia
that's in the hydrogen was put there by
the Sun and and that there took some
work to do that
[Music]
if you have that above the water in that
cell she will only suck up any water or
splashes to that everywhere okay but
there's a different thing happens if you
recharge today we disconnected all the
means of pattern getting into the
carburetor
there's no petrol get in the carburetor
there's no return dive into the tank
that was just kidding we run it
completely we purge the whole of the
carburetor with negatively charged water
actually poured water into the slot
chamber the car Brad yeah and cleaned it
out we try to give it a long long time
to really clean it out make sure it
wouldn't fire
[Laughter]
and then we got the cell can you tell me
what happens if you the timing
well what's the difference between my
water in your water looks charged young
get your water lost all your best water
my positive is only inside never what
I'm saying means it's firing
and yet there is it's it defies all
logic because the water there's no water
there's no Hudson there's no oxygen
going in it is creating another form of
energy but is can't be explained
scientifically as we know science
[Music]
we in neutral yeah
Joe is very sincere he's very
mechanically intuitive he's not educated
in a formal sense but he has evolved his
mechanical intuitions from his
perspective he's assembling what he
calls an octahedral magnetic field which
I would call a phase conjugate so the
opposing conic approaches of magnetic
flux lines creates a kind of conic
Center what I call phase conjugate or
implosive so I have been teaching about
how capacitors can face conjugate for
example how an egg makes life he has
done that magnetically
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
so the laws of energy conservation in
combination with the laws of
thermodynamics tell us that you can't
get more energy out of a system than
originally went into it and that's why
these things just can't work it really
doesn't make sense to me that this stuff
could work if you think about the water
cup hard car for example if you are
splitting hydrogen and oxygen burning it
and getting water out the other end you
could make a closed loop where the water
comes back into the system and if you're
getting more energy out than you put in
the thing will just run forever once you
get it started
everything we know about the universe
and which is what science is about
trying to understand the way the
universe works the world works
everything that we know tells us that
this is impossible some of the guys
who'd seen the car running think oh I
think Joe must have put some petrol in
there he might have had some he's may
have switched bottles put another bottle
in and I said but we passed that bottle
around and took a drink out of it it was
just water in it suffering from a kind
of delusion refusing to accept reality
with extreme magnetic implosion he's
actually able to make the impurities in
the water vaporize in a magnetic vortex
I believe that does relate to the the
use of the Joe cell classically for
hydrogen in that the concentric rings of
the metal cylinder that were used he
actually would identify which end of the
metal pipe was extruded first in the
process of manufacture because there
would be a little bit of ion bias in the
direction of magnetic line up and down
that metal piece of pipe and if you
balance those perfectly end-to-end the
concentric pipes you create it perfectly
what's called phase conjugate or what he
calls octahedral magnetics
love to to have a device like that in my
backyard you know I wouldn't have to pay
for energy ever again but it's not gonna
happen I never could understand why if
we had the possibility of having free
energy why we had to have energy we paid
for it but that's capitalism and where
our consciousness is at the moment with
our regional group that we formed which
was called Astro alternative scientific
and technological research organization
and so we formed this in the early 90s
and our aim was to research a lot of the
new energy that was coming out at the
moment and you'll Brown was a Bulgarian
inventor who decided to come to
Australia after the war started a
factory in Sydney and he started putting
together
hydrogen gas generators and selling them
as a welding apparatus so we bought his
first hydrogen gas generator and
actually had to sign a statement that we
wouldn't use it for anything other than
welding purposes although we wanted to
use it to run internal combustion motors
then we decided to make up our own fuel
cell producing hydrogen on demand got
quite a bit higher fuel efficiency and
it even got to the point where one night
driving back from casino to tabula me
this holding station wagon the
six-cylinder actually ran out of petrol
what we were doing is we were
supplementing the hydrogen oxygen we
were getting from the fuel cell with the
petrol and this actually ran out of
petrol and coughed and sputtered and
then continued running and when we got
home we found that the bowl of petrol
was completely empty and it had been
running just on the fuel cell so that
was quite exciting that we've gotten a
hundred percent efficiency out of this
fairly crude fuel cell
what happened after that was we started
telling friends about it and they
started to have some success everyone
started talking and it seemed to get
everyone was getting exciting about
these fuel cells
[Music]
look at the bang on the door comes out
me dressing again his professor Ron
Davis who apparently write up all the
science for your Brown on Browns gas
hydrogen and oxygen gas and he's front
of that me doorstep and he's driven from
Sidney all night long I'm you know I'm
professor on David said hey you know why
did you oxygen gas your brand Brown's
cancer said sorry and don't know what
you're talking about
he said anyway by the way he said I
heard that you've got a kind of running
off water yeah well whatever
yeah I did yeah listen could I love it
sure so went out the bank and everything
else and so I'm he's supposed to know
all this stuff so here's this big long
cylinder you can see plain water up into
it's got a class in nearly Gus's and so
we hooked it up to the car hit the key
he checked everything that had no fuel
and everything else so so on fired it up
and that's a prize Dean said you know
what's in the tank nothing you know
there's no lines connected right we got
four Drive
[Music]
the only doing tonight we're pushing
7,000 revs instantly strolling out
without any hesitation pushing all of us
yeah three of identify
in 7,000 rapes out in climate
we even took one up to the nimbin
Aquarius Festival the 25th anniversary
and showed this holding station wagon
with a fuel cell in it and to my
surprise quite a few people got angry
because they said why should you be
you
you're not bouncing you know losing area
then what's he do he wants to steal the
cow now the follow-on stay tight cuz
he'll follow us coming every way from
then on
people come and say oh yeah you know you
got it for nothin give it to the world
I said okay I'll give it to you is that
right you want me to give to you are you
going to give it to the next person it's
plain water straight out of a creek off
the hill there's a neutral plate - no
positive for outside negative underneath
as we see and they'll turn on a battery
charger and you'll see loo you now look
down the side work your way over the
side you'll see the it's hydrogen going
downwards it won't break the surface you
see these vapor coming off the top
that's possibly what's running the cars
whoever the guy is Joe never put one
side up never wrote any single thing
never gave one person any permission
anytime ever to write anything about him
I didn't offer making money off never
charged anybody for any of it yet
Berryhill me and Haken still selling
things now on me for years wrote books
on me there we got the information wrong
the Joe Sal as used by its creator takes
quite a tangent from logic rather than
feeding the hydrogen into the carburetor
the pipe is Stoppard at the end and
inserted into a piece of plastic tube
the engine is tuned into the Joe cell
frequency allowing it to run on a
universal power some call zero-point
energy however the scientific community
call it pure fantasy and never the twain
shall meet
we're doing is setting up a frequency
generator this thing he seems to output
something what tunes in the vehicle and
makes it run
the car that runs on Morty's not
actually running on water no it's
running on an energy created by the
water that's the way I see it then I use
water can't possibly be running water
cuz the outlet from the cell is
connected to a dead end I didn't
understand why the vehicles seem to stop
and run perfectly when nobody else seems
to be able to hit it this stuff before
it's very strangely so I just went on to
do different cars probably 20 to 30 cars
learn more information about things
built plates and cells and everything
else no electrolyte no power input
different plates what shouldn't be
connected we get electricity off the
cells we get implosion explosion we've
got all these different gases we ended
up getting a resonating field within the
tubes so we actually have tubes in place
that aren't electrically connected but
within the electrical field producing
gas so we've got excitement happening
there just playing with little um just
half-truths making things sound like
they're possible because they have all
the elements of something that's
possible but the quantities are wrong
what happened with the RTA was to get
the hydrogen fuel cell approved by them
they wanted to have a couple of cells in
new cars that they could test crash it
was gonna cost around a quarter of a
million dollars which we didn't have a
local member told a local politician and
so it actually got back to the federal
government at the time they offered his
$10,000 and a new car if we would sign
over the rights to this fuel cell we
didn't think that was a good knock deal
because we wanted to hold some sort of
proprietary rights over it so we didn't
do that and soon after that we had a
group called
aces saying it was not in our best
interest to continue this line of
research they stressed their point quite
vigorously even to the point where the
local police said that they didn't want
any fatalities in their district and
they gave us sawed-off shotguns to
protect ourselves
so we knew it was serious when the
police were giving us arms to protect
ourselves had the Department of Defense
through H division we're astounded at
what we were doing we showed them
through the workshop favorite Joe's past
are there for three days for me I think
they were amazed that we were just
freely giving it away we weren't selling
the engineer from how do you come across
with a a zo government followed what we
know definitely is a zero Australian a
zo government they front up on to see
about me selves and everything else so
unlike them it's funny men a couple of
minutes to you know we've had done
professor on Davis wanting to take out
these cars he took the first one we
never got a back or anything else
mechanics engineers physicists
government people government people
following the everywhere bugging you
threatening you with beyond 2000 we're
gonna do articles on me and everything
else and then we get to calls somebody
wants to bean bug in somewhere and kind
of send me kids back in the post to me
if I go he'll be the story so I said
stop it shut it down not interested then
they try and come and take you guys
Stan Meyer we first heard about him in
the early 90s he had a Volkswagen dune
buggy operating on a fuel cell 100
percent efficiency so I went over to
visit him and see his Factory in
Columbus Ohio he not only had cars and
buses running on this fuel cell he
actually had a commander 13 seat jet the
Stan Meyer said he wasn't too afraid of
the powers that be and he was going to
go ahead and develop his fuel cells
anyway especially since he had
discovered the frequency which would
split water easily but unfortunately he
was eating in a restaurant he got up he
said I've been poisoned he walked
outside he keeled over and he died and
then two years we had lost three major
inventors we lost Bruce DePalma
we lost Stanley Meyer and we lost you
old brown so even to this day this fuel
cell research is not strictly legal and
not allowed to come out my challenge to
people who say they can do this sort of
thing is bring it along to university
and showed off to the professors of
physics and engineering and so on
demonstrated to a skeptical audience
shows that can actually work there's
going to be a whole bunch of nobel
prizes for showing all the stuff can
actually work I for one to be really
fascinated to see you know just about
everything we know about physics being
overturned so bring it on we could run
almost all of our internal combustion
and directly on implosive hydrogen
rather quickly easily indirectly
so the lessons here are good and
civilization might even make it if we
could teach the principle and for
someone who has seen this and still
believes there might be some sort of
trick involved maybe their consciousness
is not ready to accept this no leader is
making the dollar not interesting the
business not interested in the fame and
glory whatsoever at all don't want to go
down like that shaitan history as a
famous guy he's talking it's like Thomas
you know putting his finger into Jesus
you know and do it the way he sees it he
knows Jesus died on the cross but he
still doesn't believe until he puts his
finger in there don't want to go down
the ground don't want to go down in
history don't have you know a simple
going
[Music]